♪♪♪
♪ WELL, I TOOK A WALK
AROUND THE WORLD ♪
♪ TO EASE MY TROUBLED MIND ♪
♪ I LEFT MY BODY LYING
SOMEWHERE IN THE SANDS OF TIME ♪
♪ BUT I WATCHED THE WORLD FLOAT
TO THE DARK SIDE OF THE MOON ♪
♪ I FEEL THERE'S
NOTHING I CAN DO, YEAH ♪
♪♪♪
♪ I WATCHED THE WORLD FLOAT
TO THE DARK SIDE OF THE MOON ♪
♪ AFTER ALL I KNEW, IT HAD TO
BE SOMETHING TO DO WITH YOU ♪
♪ I REALLY DON'T MIND WHAT
HAPPENS NOW AND THEN ♪
♪ AS LONG AS YOU'LL BE
MY FRIEND AT THE END ♪
♪ IF I GO CRAZY, THEN WILL
YOU STILL CALL ME SUPERMAN ♪
♪ IF I'M ALIVE AND WELL ♪
♪ WILL YOU BE THERE
AND HOLDING MY HAND ♪
♪ I'LL KEEP YOU BY MY SIDE
WITH MY SUPERHUMAN MIGHT ♪
♪ KRYPTONITE ♪
♪♪♪
♪ YOU CALLED ME STRONG,
YOU CALLED ME WEAK ♪
♪ BUT STILL YOUR
SECRETS I WILL KEEP ♪
♪ YOU TOOK FOR GRANTED ALL THE
TIMES I NEVER LET YOU DOWN ♪
♪ YOU STUMBLED IN AND
BUMPED YOUR HEAD ♪
♪ IF NOT FOR ME
THEN YOU'D BE DEAD ♪
♪ I PICKED YOU UP AND PUT
YOU BACK ON SOLID GROUND ♪
♪ IF I GO CRAZY, THEN WILL
YOU STILL CALL ME SUPERMAN ♪
♪ IF I'M ALIVE AND WELL ♪
♪ WILL YOU BE THERE
AND HOLDING MY HAND ♪
♪ I'LL KEEP YOU BY MY SIDE
WITH MY SUPERHUMAN MIGHT ♪
♪ KRYPTONITE ♪
♪♪♪
♪ IF I GO CRAZY, THEN WILL
YOU STILL CALL ME SUPERMAN ♪
♪ IF I'M ALIVE AND WELL, WILL
YOU BE THERE HOLDING MY HAND ♪
♪ I'LL KEEP YOU BY MY SIDE
WITH MY SUPERHUMAN MIGHT ♪
♪ KRYPTONITE, YEAH ♪
♪ IF I GO CRAZY, THEN WILL
YOU STILL CALL ME SUPERMAN ♪
♪ IF I'M ALIVE AND WELL ♪
♪ WILL YOU BE THERE
AND HOLDING MY HAND ♪
♪ I'LL KEEP YOU BY MY SIDE
WITH MY SUPERHUMAN MIGHT ♪
♪ KRYPTONITE ♪
♪♪♪
♪ OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ OH, OH ,OH ♪
♪♪♪